Join Tata AIA Life Insurance Business.  Is
a housewife meant only to manage the house
or
can she build her future along with the house?  Hello friends,
I am Yogendra Verma Recruitment
Manager Tata AIA and today I am going to talk to you about
a great opportunity especially for housewives and ladies empowerment.
Why is business perfect for housewives?  See, a housewife has great
skills.  Number one relationship
management.  Number two is patience, number three is
trust building, number four is
understanding family responsibilities.  And these
qualities are
most important to become a successful life insurance advisor.  Just
think, when you think so much about the security of your home, then
you can also help in the security of others' homes.  Isn't it
?  Let's talk about why choose Tata AIA?
Now the question arises, if you want to do insurance business then
why Tata AIA?  Because friends, the
name Tata itself is the identity of the trust.  Tata
AIA is the second largest private
life insurance company in India.  This
is the company producing the highest MDRT.
And look at the power of the products here.
Here, term plan is the biggest need of every family
and is
available at very reasonable pricing.
You will find the best DULI plans here, which
can help you build wealth and protection,
and there are plenty of guaranteed savings and assured plans,
which are amazing.
Retirement solutions are also
genuinely available here to secure your future.   The
scope of life insurance is so vast that
it is needed in every household.  How much
income can a housewife make?  Now the biggest question is
how much will the income be?  Friends, this is not a job, there is
no salary of any kind here.
This is a commission based business opportunity
in which the more policies you sell, the more
your income will increase.  The commission here will be from 21% to 45%.
Even housewives can easily join here part time and
can easily earn Rs 25,000 to Rs 500 per month
and if you are serious then you can
become MDRT here and earn Rs 1 lakh annually.
MDRT stands for Million Dollar Round
Table.  This is the
biggest reward and award in life insurance which is
USA recognized and many
women are working on it and earning good money.
You will also get some extra benefits
here.  Along with this you will
get monthly and quarterly contests.
Domestic and international fully paid
trips will be available from the company in which
you can tour the world.  You
can visit multiple countries.  You will get
lifetime free training and
learning support at company expense.  And most importantly,
you will not be left alone.  Three to
four managers will always support you
so that you can talk to a professional life insurance company.
What is the mandatory process here?  So the process is very simple.  There
is one mandatory exam here, the fee for which will be ₹850.
Anyone can apply all over India.
The exam will be held at a centre near you.
You will have to take two days of full day compulsory physical branch training.
This is mandatory before the exam.  And there will be objective
type question answers.  There will be questions of 50 marks.
Passing marks must be 15 marks.
You will have to prepare a list of 50 prospects before the exam.
50 people and has a 100% digital training
platform.  Training will be available from 9:30 am to 10:30 am,
Monday to Saturday.
Training will be available from 8 to 9 in the evening.  5 to 10
sessions will be available in a month.  After getting the code, it
is necessary to take one policy in the first month
with a premium of Rs 400 and it will be necessary to take 12 policies in a year
so that your code remains active.  Let me
talk about women empowerment,
friends, India's
dream is to develop India in 2047 and the agenda is
insurance for every home, so think if women do
not come forward then how will every home be secure,
this business not only gives income, it
also gives respect, confidence and empowerment
which is amazing and useful for you.
If you too
want to create your identity and financial freedom by being a housewife.
Why is it the biggest upgrade?  If you are a
network marketer, MLM leader then
I have brought Amazing Working for you.
You have formed your team but is the
income permanent?  Join Tata where
Tata name and 99.13%
claim will not let Lim break.
Recruit your team in Tata A Leadership Model
and earn unlimited profits.  5% to 30%
is real business.  There
is no hassle in making any member.  Exam fee will be ₹850 and
registration fee will be ₹5000.
Free International Trips with Tata where you
can create history.  Only full time
working is available.  Two days of branch
training is mandatory.  Long term vision
is important for you and you have leadership skills.
You can form a team.  Can trend people.
So don't delay.  Write on WhatsApp
Tata AIA Leader I
will guide you genuinely.  Leave MLM,
become a corporate leader of Tata and build your future.
Hello.  The whole world is
looking towards India today.  Our country is on its way to
becoming the third largest economy in the world.
But do you know which sector is the
brightest star of this Indian growth story
?  So that is the health
insurance sector.  Even today,
70% of India's population does not have proper health insurance
cover.  Just imagine, where the demand is so
high and the supply is so low,
how much scope is there for business?  Are you still
chasing old jobs or
want to be a part of the sector which
is going to grow like a rocket for the next 20 years then Hello, I am Yogendra Verma
Recruitment Manager.  I am helping over 500
partners take advantage of this historic booming
sector.
To take advantage of this boom in the health sector, you will need the country's most
trusted company, ICICI LBD.
We are the number one general insurance company in the country.
When the country grows, the leader will
grow first.  The use of Artificial Intelligence in claim settlement
and 100% digital
model puts us far ahead of others.
Along with 15% to 35% commission on selling health insurance, there is also a sea of ​​passive income like 15%
renewal commission which can
make you successful for generations to come.
Here you not only get money but
also get the opportunity of Mansan and international paid trips.  There are
strict rules for success.
Great work requires discipline for great success.  There are
some
clear conditions to join us.  Before getting into the license code,
you will need to create a prospecting list of 50 people from your network.   No
war is won without preparation.
After getting the code, it will be necessary to take a
health policy of Rs 15,000 premium in the first month so
that your code becomes active
and it is necessary to take 12 policies in a year
so that your code continues.  Your
qualification should be at least 12th
and if your age is between 20 years to 65 years
then you are welcome.  It is mandatory to give the exam here
and the fee for it is
₹1000 and it takes 10 to 12 days for the exam to come, for which
my team will guide you.
India is changing.  Are you
ready to change your destiny?  The sector is growing
, the country is growing.  You will
not be left only among the spectators, will you?  Join ICC LBA
and become a shareholder in India's progress.
If you want to
secure and prosper your future by joining the mission of Developed India 2047, then
WhatsApp your name and ICC Low Health Agent now.
WhatsApp number is 859540
7616. Please like, share and follow the channel
so that you keep getting better updates.
Hello.  Hello friends, next video
is titled
Why Motor Insurance Agents Become Tata AIA Life Insurance Agent
?  So let's talk about being a motor insurance
agent and let me ask you a question.  If you
insure a vehicle, have you ever
thought of insuring a human life?  Hello friends, I am
Yogendra Verma, Recruitment Manager Tata
AIA.  Today's video is especially for those motor
insurance agents who
want to take their business to the next level.
Friends, look at the biggest reality of motor insurance business, motor insurance
is necessary.  But listen to the punch line.  The car is
renewed once a year.  But the
impact of life insurance
lasts for the whole life.  The complexity in motor insurance is
very high.  But the premium
is also limited.  And the client's focus remains
only on the price.  Make it cheaper brother.
But life insurance is a trust based
business.  This is the amazing business of future planning.
Why is an upgrade from Motor to Life necessary?  You already have
clients, car owners, business
owners, working professionals,
female families.  Now imagine all of them
need a term life term plan.  There
is a risk of car accident.  But the
risk to the family's future is the biggest risk.
Term insurance is a basic need of every person.
Why is Tata AIA the brand you trust?   Let's
talk about this also.
Many people have a question in their mind that
why should they join Tata AIA in life insurance
?  So its very simple answer is
Tata equal to trust.  Tata
AI is the second largest private
life insurance company in India.  Highest
MDRT is one of the leading producer companies.
And the products are such that the client
automatically says that I
want only Tata products.  Be it a term plan
which is the need of every family.  Be it guaranteed
assured plans that provide fixed security
or ULIP plans
that are a great combo of wealth plus protection
and
what to say about retirement planning, pension ready solutions are
available here.  ULIP equal to SIP
plus insurance is a jackpot for motor agents.
Now know the biggest advantage: Motor
clients are already financially aware.
You can now offer them.
ULIP offers SIP like investment option,
mutual fund style wealth creation along with
life cover protection and in this single plan
you get investment insurance plus
future security, that is,
this upgrade becomes super powerful for motor agents
and from here a second source of
earning starts.  You can do this
work in an easily flexible manner in both part time and full time
options.
In which there is no challenge of any kind.
Whether you do it part time or
full time.  Later on,
you can manage it as a career full time.
You will keep learning here and earning will also
start and continue.  This is amazing
amazing working.  Here
you will get higher commission plus higher income.  Please pay attention.  Let me
first tell you how you will earn here.  This is not any kind of job.
No salary of any kind is
given here.  This is a commission based business
opportunity.  Your income will depend on the number of policies you sell.
The commission ranges from 21% to 45%.  It is possible in part time
and can also be done in full time.
You can earn a minimum of Rs 25,000 to Rs 500 per month here and in future, it is possible to
earn Rs 2 lakh, Rs 5 lakh, Rs 10 lakh per month.  By
becoming an MDRT, one can earn ₹13
lakh annually here and
MDRT is famous for Tata MDRT culture.
Most of the MDRTs are
manufactured within Tata companies.  And you will
enjoy it even more after hearing about the extra benefits.  Here
you will find monthly and quarterly contests in
which you can qualify for domestic and international trips
in fully paid versions.
You will get lifetime free trainings and learning support here.  You will always have three to four
managers to guide you.
You are not alone here.  The entire
ecosystem works with you here.   There are
just some mandatory procedures here.
You will need to share your basic KYC documents
with us.  Which I will share with you the list
of documents.  In the process,
you will have to appear for an exam which is
mandatory and the fee for it will be ₹850.
You can apply for this at the all India level, wherever you are.
The exam will be held
at the nearest centre.  You will have to take two days of full day compulsory
training.  In the local near by
branch in which we will align and
here 50 questions will come out of which
you have to pass 15.  It will be necessary to get 15 marks.
Before the exam, it will be
necessary to prepare a prospecting list of 50 people
so that after the exam, work can be done on
what I and my team will teach you.   It is a
100% digital training platform.  Here the
training is held in the morning
from 9:30 am to 10:30 am Monday to Saturday
through Microsoft Teams.  Training takes place in the evening
through ZM Meeting from 8
to 9. You will get 5 to 10 training sessions
in the evening only.  After receiving the code, it will be
necessary to make a policy in the first month.   It is
mandatory to have a premium of Rs 400 and 12 policies in a year to keep your code
running.  So let me ask you the final question.
As a motor insurance agent, will you limit yourself to just vehicles
or will you also provide lifetime wealth protection to your clients?
This is an opportunity to
capture the term plan market.   There
is an opportunity to create ULIP wealth
and move ahead in the retirement planning segment.
Higher commission plus trips can be
found here.  Better Future
Prospective can be yours here.
So if you want to become a motor insurance agent and
make it your next income pillar, then
you have to WhatsApp me.  Tata AIA
Agent my WhatsApp number is 981826521
or write BOP in DM.  BOP
stands for Business Opportunity Presentation.
I will share its complete PDF with you
on WhatsApp by writing in DM.  And I
am Yogendra Verma, Recruitment Manager,
Tata AIA 500 Plus Advisors, already working on
all over India basis, so
please like, share
and follow the channel so that you keep getting updates.
I am talking to you, are
you still roaming around with the flag of only one company
and surviving on low commission,
do you know that you can sell
all the insurance companies and all the mutual
funds of India from a single platform,
that too without leaving any old agency,
yes friends, you will not believe it
but it is possible.  Hello, I am
Yogendra Verma, Recruitment Manager, Bajaj
Capital.  Today, 5000 plus agents from India and abroad are
joining me and creating history.
Bajaj Capital gives you a super
platform where you can manage all the companies including life, health, motor and
travel
insurance as well as mutual funds
together on a single platform.  And the biggest thing is that
you are going to get the guarantee of highest commission and best trail commission in mutual funds here.
Which can be a win-win situation for you.
Those who have come to the channel for the first time,
please follow it.  Otherwise this
important deal will be missed.  It
is very important.  If you
are a fresher in the insurance industry then
POS code will be generated for you, no exam, no fees
, same day code will be generated and you
can start working in 3 days.  And if you
are already an experienced agent, an
agent of any IIT company or
already have a licensed POS code from any broker, then the
marketing code is available here for you.
In which there will be no exam or any fee.
Same day code will be generated and
you can start working after 3 days.  Even if you already have
an IIT code or broker code,
you can still join Bajaj Capital and
earn extra through marketing code.
No worries, it is 100% legal.
You will not face any kind of challenge or problem.   If I
talk about Bajaj Capital, we have the trust of 60 years
and 1000 plus offices. Our
platform is 100% digital.  If your
customer has a Bajaj Capital consumer
card, he
can purchase any policy on instant EMI.  And now listen to the topic
of earnings.  How much income are you going to get from where
?  If I talk about life insurance,
you can take commission from 25% to 40% to 45%.   If I
talk to health insurance then you can get 15% to
35% commission.  And
you will also get a good commission on portability here.  If we talk about model insurance,
you will get commission ranging from 2% to 75%.
In this you can do two wheeler, three wheeler,
four wheeler, commercial everything.
Talking about SMA and Group Insurance,
you can get a payout of 5% to 15% and up to 30% here.
Talking about travel insurance in SMA business,
you can get a payout of 20% to 40%.
You are going to get amazing working here.  Not just sales, we
provide amazing claim support and most
accurate timely payouts.  We know what your
hard work is worth.  Whether you are
in India or an NRI, start your financial
journey today.  Don't be part of the crowd.
Become a brand yourself.  Don't delay with Bajaj Capital.
This opportunity
is available for a limited time.  Now
call or WhatsApp the number given on the screen.
Write Bajaj Capital Agent Code on WhatsApp.  If you want to
get POS code then write the POS code.   If you want to
get the marketing code, then write the marketing code
and it is going to be destroyed for you.  Do
n't delay.  Get your code today.
Hello thanks